[
  {
    "question": "Which fruit or vegetable is commonly carved as Jack-o'- lantern during Halloween celebrations.",
    "options": [
      "cucumber",
      "pumpkin ",
      "squash",
      "eggplant "
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pumpkin ",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "What shouldn't you judge a book by? ",
    "options": [
      "it's title",
      "it's contents",
      "it's page ",
      "it's cover"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "it's cover",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the color of the traffic light indicating \"stop\"?",
    "options": [
      "Green ",
      "Yellow",
      "Red",
      "Purple"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Red",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the first three words of the Bible?",
    "options": [
      "thus said the... ",
      "in the beginning... ",
      "let there be.. ",
      "this is the ... "
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "in the beginning... ",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "Apple does not fall far from the ....? ",
    "options": [
      "tree",
      "bush",
      "head",
      "ground"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tree",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Shakespearan character is the famous lover of Juliet? ",
    "options": [
      "Othello",
      "Hamlet",
      "Romeo",
      "Greg"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Romeo",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital city of Spain?",
    "options": [
      "Catalonia",
      "Madrid ",
      "Paris",
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Madrid ",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "What chemical is added to water in swimming pool? ",
    "options": [
      "chlorine",
      "ammonia",
      "silver",
      "hydrogen "
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chlorine",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the title of Shakespeare's play? ",
    "options": [
      "Hamlet",
      "Gimlet",
      "Porklet",
      "Pamphlet"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hamlet",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is a doctor's coat? ",
    "options": [
      "Red",
      "Green",
      "Black",
      "White"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "White",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is said to always land on their feet? ",
    "options": [
      "Dogs",
      "Cats",
      "Wolf",
      "Bird"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Cats",
    "userAnswer": null
  },
  {
    "question": "Which symbol represents love? ",
    "options": [
      "A heart ",
      "A stone ",
      "A butterfly",
      "A flower"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A heart ",
    "userAnswer": null
  }
]